knology.net 2009-11-27

# Knology.com

**PRIVACY POLICY**  

Knology believes the protection of your privacy is one of the most important responsibilities we have. This Policy explains how the information you may supply to us through the Knology web site will be used. If any changes are made to this Policy, they will be posted on the Knology web site. Please read this Policy carefully so that you understand our privacy and security policies. Your use of the Knology web site constitutes your agreement to the terms of the Policy. If you have questions about this Policy, please contact us at [info@knology.com](mailto:info@knology.com) or write to us at 1241 O.G. Skinner Drive, West Point, GA, 31833. 

Knology web site means knology.com, knology.net, and any other knology.com promotional web sites.

We, our, and us mean Knology, Inc. and all of its subsidiary and affiliated entities, including Knology. 

When we use the words "you" and "your" we mean customers who have a continuing relationship with us, such as:

Individuals viewing our websites.  
Individuals contacting us by completing an on-line form on the Knology web site. 

**Terms used in this Policy are:** **  
** Nonpublic personal information means information about you that we collect in connection with providing Knology services to you. Nonpublic personal information does not include information that is available from public sources, such as telephone directories. Hereafter, we will use the term "information" to mean nonpublic personal information as defined in this section. 

An affiliate is a company we own or control, a company that owns or controls us, or a company that is owned or controlled by the same company that owns or controls us. 

A nonaffiliated third party is a person we do not employ or a company that is not an affiliate of ours. This is also known as nonaffiliated third party, or simply, an "other party." 

**Information You Provide to Us:** **  
** You may provide public and nonpublic personal information, including your name, postal address, email address, and telephone number when you submit information via on-line forms on the Knology web site. We restrict access to nonpublic personal information about you to those employees who need to know that information to provide services to you. 

**Information Collected Through Technology:** **  
** We collect information through technology to make our sites more interesting and useful to you. For example, when you come to the Knology web site, we collect your IP address. An IP address is often associated with the portal through which you enter the Internet, like your ISP (Internet Service Provider), your company, or your university. Standing alone, your IP address is not personally identifiable. Your IP address allows us to track the pages you've visited. We aggregate this data with data from the pages visited by other users to track overall visitor traffic patterns. 

**Browsing on our Web Site:**  
If you browse through the Knology web site without entering any personal data, we will gather and store certain information about your visit. This information does not identify you personally and cannot be linked back to you unless you decide at some point to identify yourself. 

If you are only browsing, we collect the following information: IP address, the date and time you access our site, and the pages you visit (click-through).

**Provision and Transmission of Information** :  
We will not read Your outgoing or incoming e-mail, video mail, private chat, or instant messages, but we (or our third party providers) do store e-mail messages and video mail messages on computer systems for a period of time. We could be required to disclose these messages and communications along with other personally identifiable information about You to comply with law or to protect our Service as described in the Knology Acceptable Use Policy and the Knology Customer Service Agreement, both of which can be found at <http://www.knology.com/about/legal.cfm>.  We also monitor the performance of our Service and Your Service connection in order to manage, maintain, and improve the Service and Your connection to it. We (or our third party providers) use tools to help prevent and block "spam" e-mails, viruses, spyware, and other harmful or unwanted communications and programs on the Service. These tools may automatically scan Your e-mails, video mails, instant messages, file attachments, and other files and communications in order to help us protect You and the Service against these harmful or unwanted communications and programs. However, these tools do not collect or disclose personally identifiable information about You. 

**Information You Provide to Non-Affiliated Third Parties:**  
You should also be aware that any personally identifiable information You provide in publicly accessible services or websites, including but not limited to, forums, chat areas, instant message services, or bulletin boards may be read, collected, and used by others who access those services. We are not responsible for any personally identifiable information You choose to submit in forums, chat areas, instant message services, bulletin boards, or any other publicly accessible service or website, even when such site was accessed or linked to by You through Knology’s website.

**Children Under 13:** **  
** The Children's Online Privacy Protection Act ("COPPA") requires that we inform parents and legal guardians about how we collect, use, and disclose personal information from children under 13 years of age and that we obtain the consent of parents and guardians in order for children to use certain features of the Knology web site. 

Children can surf www.Knology.com and view content without any personal information being collected. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children 

We may amend our Privacy Policy at any time. At all times, parents should update their personal information to provide us current email addresses. We will apply material changes in our Privacy Policy only in conformance with applicable law, including any applicable provisions of COPPA that require parental consent. 

**E-Mail Addresses:** **  
** E-mail addresses will not be sold or distributed to any non-affiliated third party, with the exception that Knology may contract with non-affiliated third parties to distribute Knology emails related to new features, offers, promotions, etc. The Knology web site uses e-mail addresses to uniquely identify users of our service. Knology may use your e-mail address to contact you regarding new features or other service related notices and may do so by contracting with non-affiliated third parties. 

We reserve the right to contact you if compelled to do so as part of a legal proceeding or if there has been a violation of the Knology Terms and Conditions of Service. 

**Your Information and Other Parties:** **  
** We will not disclose information about you to anyone except as disclosed in this Policy or as permitted by law. If requested by law enforcement or judicial authorities, we will provide this information upon receipt of the appropriate documentation. Knology may also provide information to law enforcement to protect its property and the health and safety of individuals as permitted by statute. 

**Security:** **  
** Information gathered by Knology on the web site is stored within Knology controlled databases on servers maintained in protected environments. Our security and privacy policies are periodically reviewed and enhanced as necessary, and only authorized individuals have access to the information provided by our users. 

However, no physical or electronic security system is impenetrable. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of our servers or databases, nor can we guarantee that information you supply won't be intercepted while being transmitted to us over the Internet, and you use these services at your own risk. 

**Your Right to Opt-Out of Knology Marketing Contacts:**  
Knology may, from time to time, send promotional emails or similar email communications to you through our third party email providers.  If you do not wish to receive such emails, you may opt-out of such communications by following the opt-out or “unsubscribe” link at the bottom of any such solicitation.  You may also contact customer service at 1-877-566-5646 or (1-877-KNOLOGY) to implement your opt-out decision.  If you choose to opt-out of such communications, within ten (10) business days you will be removed from all such marketing solicitations, including direct mail and other forms of communications you might otherwise receive from Knology.  However, Knology may still contact you via email with mandated regulatory notifications and/or other important information regarding your Knology services.

**Contact Information:** **  
** If you have any questions about this Policy, the practices of the Knology web site, or your dealings with this web site, please contact: 

Knology, Inc.  
1241 O.G. Skinner Drive  
West Point, GA  31833  
Phone:  1-877-566-5646 or (1-877-KNOLOGY)
